<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<addon id="plugin.video.frndlytv" name="Frndly TV" version="1.0.0" provider-name="Marcus Montgomery / BeatTLF Entertainment">
    <requires>
        <import addon="xbmc.python" version="3.0.0"/>
        <import addon="script.module.requests" version="2.22.0"/>
        <import addon="inputstream.adaptive" version="2.0.0" optional="true"/>
    </requires>
    <extension point="xbmc.python.pluginsource" library="default.py">
        <provides>video</provides>
    </extension>
    <extension point="xbmc.service" library="service.py" start="startup"/>
    <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
        <summary lang="en">Frndly TV - Live TV Streaming for Kodi</summary>
        <description lang="en">Frndly TV for Kodi - The Ultimate Live TV Streaming Add-on

WHAT IS THIS ADD-ON?
Frndly TV for Kodi is a video add-on that allows you to stream live television channels directly from your Frndly TV subscription within Kodi. This add-on eliminates the need for Docker containers, external servers, or additional hardware - everything runs directly on your device.

FEATURES:
• Live TV Streaming - Watch all your Frndly TV channels in real-time
• Full EPG Support - Electronic Program Guide with show titles, descriptions, episode info, thumbnails, and TV parental ratings (TV-Y, TV-G, TV-PG, TV-14, TV-MA)
• Channel Logos &amp; Numbers - Professional channel presentation with official logos
• PVR/DVR Integration - Record your favorite shows with full metadata support
• Built-in Web Server - Optional server for IPTV client integration (TiviMate, Channels DVR, etc.)
• Fire TV &amp; Android TV Compatible - Works on Fire Stick, Android TV boxes, and all Kodi devices
• Self-Contained - No external server or computer required

REQUIREMENTS:
• Kodi 19 (Matrix) or later
• Active Frndly TV subscription
• Internet connection

CREATED BY:
Marcus Montgomery / BeatTLF Entertainment

BASED ON:
frndlytv-for-channels by Matt Huisman (https://github.com/matthuisman/frndlytv-for-channels)

DISCLAIMER:
This add-on is not affiliated with or endorsed by Frndly TV. You must have a valid Frndly TV subscription to use this add-on.</description>
        <disclaimer lang="en">This add-on is not affiliated with Frndly TV. A valid subscription is required.</disclaimer>
        <platform>all</platform>
        <license>MIT</license>
        <website>https://frndlytv.com</website>
        <source>https://github.com/beattlf/frndlytv-kodi</source>
        <news>
v1.0.0 (January 2025)
─────────────────────
NEW FEATURES:
• Initial public release
• Direct Frndly TV API integration for live streaming
• Full EPG with show info, ratings, thumbnails, and episode details
• PVR/DVR recording support with metadata
• Built-in web server for external IPTV clients
• Fire TV and Android TV optimized
• Channel logos and numbering system
• TV Parental Guidelines ratings display (TV-Y, TV-G, TV-PG, TV-14, TV-MA)
• Auto session management and keep-alive
        </news>
        <assets>
            <icon>resources/icon.png</icon>
            <fanart>resources/fanart.jpg</fanart>
        </assets>
    </extension>
</addon>
